Guide to the Marilyn Skolnick Papers, 1952-2009 AIS.2001.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Transportation, 1961-2004; II.
  - Port Authority of Allegheny County (PAT), 1961-2002; 10.
    - Complaints, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Complaints, 1993-1995 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Complaints, 1994-1995 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Complaints, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 13-14)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 15-17)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 19-23)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 24-27)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1992-1995 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1994-2000 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, 1999-2002 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, undated (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - Consumer Relations/ Operations Committee, Newsclippings, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - Corporate Passes, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1989 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1989 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 9-10)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 12-13)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1999 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Crow's Run, 1987-1993 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Customer Satisfaction Survey, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Disabled and Elderly Persons, undated (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Disadvantage Business, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Disadvantaged Business Enterprise, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Duquesne Incline, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - East Busway, 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Economic Development, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Employees, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Employee Benefits Compensation, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Employees, Contract Negotiating, undated (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Employees, Most Valuable Performers, undated (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Employee Policy, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Employee Publication, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - Equal Opportunity Employment Subcommittee, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 35)
    - Engineering, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 36-37)
    - Evaluations, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 38)
    - Fares, 1982-1989 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - Fare Correspondence, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 40)
    - Fare Hike, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - Fare Increase, 1979-1982 (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - Fare Increase, Newsclippings, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 43)
    - Feasibility Study, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 44)
    - Fifth Avenue Busway, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 45)
    - Financial, 1981-1983 (Box 45, Folder 46)
    - Financial, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 47)
    - Financial, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 48)
    - Financial, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 49)
    - Financial, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
    - Financial, 1987-1992 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Financial, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 4-5)
    - Financial, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 6-7)
    - Financial, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Financial, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 10-11)
    - Financial, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 12-13)
    - Financial, 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Financial, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Financial, 1999-2000 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Financial, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Financial, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Financial, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Financial, undated (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Financial, Bank Accounts, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Financial, Conference, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Financial, Conference, undated (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Financial, Department of Administration, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Financial, Employment, 1986-1987 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Financial, Marketing and Planning Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Financial, Marketing and Planning Reports, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Financial, Marketing and Business Development Plan, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Financial, Marketing and Business Development Plan, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Financial, Report on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Financial, Section 9A Block Grants, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Financial, Service Standards Performance Evaluation, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Financial, State Taxes Dedicated, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Financial, Treasurer's Duties, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Financial, Union, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Financial, Union Statements, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Fixed Guideway Project, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Garage Rehab Program, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Hazardous Waste, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Hearing Regulation, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - History, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Investigation of SEPTA, undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Human Resources, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - IBEW, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Insurance, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Job Descriptions, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Labor Legislation, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Labor Reform, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Legal, Court Cases, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Legal, Court Cases, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Legal, Court Cases, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Legal Issues, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Legal Service Costs, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Legal Services, Request for Proposals 93-09, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 25-31)
    - Legal Services, Request for Proposals 93-09, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Legal, Silvestri Court Decision, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Legislative, APTA Conference, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Legislative Committee, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Committee, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Legislative Committee, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 7-9)
    - Legislative Conference, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Legislative Priorities, 1982-1983 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Legislation, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Legislation, Minority Report of the State House of Representatives, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Light Rail, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Light Rail Conference, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Light Rail, Subway, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Light Rail Transit, 1978-1982 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Limits of Authority, 1986-1988 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Loaned Executive Committee, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Local 85, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Management Plan, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Marketing Plans, 1985-1987 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Martin Luther King Jr., Busway, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Martin Luther King Jr., Busway Extension, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Martin Luther Kind Jr., Busway Extension, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Pennsylvania MPO, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Member Expenses, 1990-1996 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Monongahela, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Mount Lebanon Cemetery, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Mount Lebanon Tunnel, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Neopan Buses, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - Newsclippings, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - Newsclippings, 1983-1987 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - Newsclippings, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - Newsclippings, 1990-1993 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - Newsclippings, 1994-1996 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - Newsclippings, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 37)
    - Newsclippings, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 38)
    - Newsclippings, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 39)
    - Newsletters, All Aboard, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 40)
    - Newsletters, Gold Currency, 1998-2000 (Box 48, Folder 41)
    - Oakland Bus, April 1990 (Box 48, Folder 42)
    - Organizational Structure, undated (Box 48, Folder 43)
    - Outdoor Advertising, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 44)
    - Pamphlets, undated (Box 48, Folder 45)
    - Paratransit, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 46)
    - Paratransit Plan Update, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Paratransit Plan Update, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Parking, 1983-1988 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Parkway West Corridor, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Part Time Work, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - PaTrain, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - PaTrain, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 7-8)
    - PaTrain, B and D Train, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - PaTrain, Public Hearing, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Pension, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Pension Fund, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Pension Trust Agreement, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Philosophy, undated (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh on the Move, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Planning Committee, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Planning Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Planning Committee, 1983-1989 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Planning and Construction Committee, 1987-1991 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Planning and Construction Committee, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Planning and Construction Committee, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Planning and Construction Committee, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Planning and Construction Committee, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 23-24)
    - Planning and Construction Committee, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Planning and Construction Committee, 1999-2002 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Planning and Construction Committee, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Police/Security Force, 1970-1985 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Policy, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Press Coverage, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Procedure Policy, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Projects, 1985-1986 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Proposal 93-09 and 83-04, undated (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Proposal, Environmental, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Proposal, GAN, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Proposal Request, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Public Hearing, 1984-1989 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Public Hearings, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Public Relations, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Public Review Document, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Public Utility Commission, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Publications, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Purchasing Manual, undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Rail 21, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - RFP, undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Rail System, 1983-1987 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Research Projects, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Reduced Fair Program, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Reports, 1983-1985 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Reports, 1991-1998 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Reports, 1992-1995 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Reports, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Reports, Arthur Anderson, 1986-1997 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Reports, Arthur Anderson, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Reports, Construction Notes, 1984 (Box 50, Other 20)
    - Reports, Customer Satisfaction Survey, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Reports, Emergency Operations Plan, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Reports, Energy Usage and Cost Reduction, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Reports, Equal Employment Opportunity, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Reports, Executive Summary, 1977-1986 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Reports, Global Changes and Local Opportunities, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Reports, Institutional Aspects of Metropolitan Transportation, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Reports, Integrated System of Mass Transportation, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
    - Reports, Livability Work Group, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Reports, Local Government Subcommittees, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Reports, Public Testimony, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Reports, Ridership, 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Reports, Ridership, 1993-1997 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Reports, Ridership, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Reports, Ridership, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Reports, Ridership, 1997-1999 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Reports, Ridership, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Reports, Ridership, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Reports, Road Operations, 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Reports, Road Operations, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Reports, Special Revenue on Transportation Bonds, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 15-17)
    - Resolutions, undated (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Review, 1989-1994 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Right to Know Law, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Service Reduction, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Service Reduction Proposal, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Service Standards, 1987-1989 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Service Standards, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Snow Emergency Plan, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - South Hills Ridership, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Southwestern Pennsylvania Transit Coalition, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Summary of Schedule Changes, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Spineline Corridor, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 5-6)
    - Spineline Corridor, 1984-1986 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Spineline Corridor, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 8-9)
    - Spineline Corridor, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 10-14)
    - Spineline Corridor, Recovery Grant Proposal Appendix, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 15-16)
    - Spineline Corridor, Study, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Spineline Corridor, Study, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Statements, 25th Anniversary, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Statements, Gamble, Ron, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Statements, Needs, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 21-23)
    - Statements, Official, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Statements, Press Releases, undated (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Studies, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Studies, undated (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Training and Development, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Transit Advisory Committee, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Transit Labor Laws, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Transit Scholarship Fund, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Transit Tax, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Transit Tax, 1984-1985 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Transit Workshop, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Travel and Expense Reimbursement, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - Tunnels, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - Urban Mass Transit, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Vandalism, Graffiti, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Vandalism, Graffiti, 1986-1991 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Vital Signs, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Waterway Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Workman's Compensation, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority (SEPTA), 1988-2000; 11.
    The material in this subseries date from 1988 to 2000 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 1990 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - 1997 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - 2000 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Citizens Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Citizens Advisory Committee, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Finance Committee, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Funding Needs, 1990-1992 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1990-1998 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Minutes, 1996-1998 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Transportation Research Board (TRB), 1983-2001; 12.
    - 1983 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - 1992-1999 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - 1993 (Box 53, Folder 19-20)
    - 1994 (Box 53, Folder 21-22)
    - 1995 (Box 53, Folder 23-25)
    - 1996 (Box 53, Folder 26-28)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - 1997 (Box 53, Folder 30-31)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - 1998 (Box 53, Folder 33-36)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 53, Folder 37-38)
    - 1999 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - 00-1073 Report on Public Involvement in Transportation Planning, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - 2020 Project, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - 21st Annual Summer Conference, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - 63rd Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - 64th Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - 65th Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
    - 65th Annual Meeting, Citizens Action Committee, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - 68th Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - 69th Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - 72nd Annual Meeting, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - A1F03, Transportation and Air Quality, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - A1F03, Transportation and Air Quality, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - A1D04, Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - AD104, Citizen Participation, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - A1D04, Citizen Participation, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - A1D04, Membership Survey, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - A1C06, Social and Economic Factors, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - A1A03, Agenda and Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - A1F02, Environmental Analysis, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - A1G01, Rural Public Transportation Committee, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Annual Report and Summary, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Attendance Roster, Agendas, and Group Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Citizen Participation in Transportation, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Citizen Participation in Transportation Planning, 1984-1987 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Citizen Participation in Transportation Planning, Appointment to Committee, 1989-1992 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Citizen Participation Council, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Committee on Taxation, Finance, and Pricing, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Committee on Taxation, Financing, and Pricing, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Conferences, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Department of Rail and Public Transportation, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Division A Group 1 Section D, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Division A Committee Correspondence, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Division A Committee Membership, undated (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Environmental Issues, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Environmental Research Needs, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Finance, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Finance Committee, 1985-1988 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Finance Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Finance and Transportation Programming, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Funding from NCHRP, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Joint Summer Meeting of Committees, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Meetings, 1995-2000 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Meetings, 1997-2001 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Memorandums to Committee Chairman, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Memorandums to Skolnick, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 5-6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995-1998 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990-1995 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996-1997 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996-2000 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Mission Statement, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters, 1993-1998 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Notice to Authors of Publications, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Pamphlets, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Papers, Alvarez, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Papers, Offer Form, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Papers, Request for Reviews, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Papers, Review Process, undated (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Papers, Submission Reviews, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Papers, Robinson, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Project Candidates, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Public Involvement in Transportation, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 22-23)
    - Publications, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - SEC Chair Meeting, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Summer Meeting, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Transportation and Air Quality Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Transportation and Air Quality Committee, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Transportation Equity Act for the 21st Century (TEA-21), 1992 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - TEA-21, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 30-31)
    - TEA-21, 1998-1999 (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - TEA-21, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - TEA-21, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 34-35)
    - Transportation Financing Techniques, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 36)
    - Travel Insurance, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 37)
    - VIP2, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 38)
    - VIP2 Financial, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - United States Department of Transportation (U.S. DOT), 1985-2001; 13.
    The material in this subseries date from 1985 to 2001 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 1986-1988 (Box 55, Folder 40)
    - 1991 (Box 55, Folder 41)
    - 1992-1994 (Box 55, Folder 42)
    - 1993-1995 (Box 55, Folder 43)
    - 1994 (Box 55, Folder 44)
    - 1998 (Box 55, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1997-2001 (Box 55, Folder 46)
    - Empowerment Zones, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 47)
    - Faxes, House of Representatives, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 48)
    - Federal Highway Administration, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 49)
    - Friends of Committee Survey, undated (Box 55, Folder 50)
    - Memo, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 51)
    - National Transportation Policy, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 52)
    - News, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 53)
    - Press Releases, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 54)
    - Public Involvement, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 55)
    - Section 15 Seminar, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Transportation and the Environment, 1992-1995 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Urban Mass Transit, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Southwestern Pennsylvania Commission/Southwestern Pennsylvania Regional Planning Commission, 1979-2005; III.
  The Southwestern Pennsylvania Regional Planning Commission (SPRPC) was formed in 1962 directly under provisions of the Planning Act. Years later, in 1992, membership in SPRPC combined with Fayette, Greene, and Indiana counties, molded the council to act as a Local Development District (LDD). This was done under the ARC Act of 1995. Also in 1995, the organization formed an Economic Development District (EDD) under the Public Works Act. In 1999, the SPRPC and the Council merged to form the Southwestern Pennsylvania Commission (SPC).
  The members of the SPC include the counties of: Allegheny, Armstrong, Beaver, Butler, Fayette, Greene, Indiana, Washington, Westmoreland, and the City of Pittsburgh. SPC is the Pennsylvania's region for "collaboration, planning, and public decision-making. SPC is responsible for planning and prioritizing the use of all state and federal transportation funds allocated to the region" (SPC website). Since ten counties are involved in the SPC, the decisions made on any issue have the power to affect each participating county.